[{"subjectID":"5af5ss5dne","prolificID":"6683e9097336723a1012955c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2225d628c0b7a282de5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980200094,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":0,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"10","question":"If you could change anything about the way you were raised, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":12981,"timeElapsed":51379},{"subjectID":"5af5ss5dne","prolificID":"6683e9097336723a1012955c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2225d628c0b7a282de5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980206013,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":1,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"10","question":"If you could change anything about the way you were raised, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":27,"rt":5917,"timeElapsed":57298},{"subjectID":"5af5ss5dne","prolificID":"6683e9097336723a1012955c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2225d628c0b7a282de5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980210063,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":2,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"10","question":"If you could change anything about the way you were raised, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":72,"rt":4047,"timeElapsed":61348},{"subjectID":"5af5ss5dne","prolificID":"6683e9097336723a1012955c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2225d628c0b7a282de5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980218057,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":3,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"10","question":"If you could change anything about the way you were raised, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":7991,"timeElapsed":69342},{"subjectID":"5af5ss5dne","prolificID":"6683e9097336723a1012955c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2225d628c0b7a282de5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980224958,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":4,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"10","question":"If you could change anything about the way you were raised, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":40,"rt":6899,"timeElapsed":76243},{"subjectID":"5af5ss5dne","prolificID":"6683e9097336723a1012955c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2225d628c0b7a282de5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980235255,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":5,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"10","question":"If you could change anything about the way you were raised, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":25,"rt":10296,"timeElapsed":86540},{"subjectID":"5af5ss5dne","prolificID":"6683e9097336723a1012955c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2225d628c0b7a282de5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980238221,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":6,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"10","question":"If you could change anything about the way you were raised, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":2964,"timeElapsed":89506},{"subjectID":"5af5ss5dne","prolificID":"6683e9097336723a1012955c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2225d628c0b7a282de5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980240843,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":7,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"10","question":"If you could change anything about the way you were raised, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":95,"rt":2620,"timeElapsed":92128},{"subjectID":"5af5ss5dne","prolificID":"6683e9097336723a1012955c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2225d628c0b7a282de5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980245185,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":8,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"10","question":"If you could change anything about the way you were raised, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":96,"rt":4340,"timeElapsed":96470},{"subjectID":"5af5ss5dne","prolificID":"6683e9097336723a1012955c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2225d628c0b7a282de5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980255792,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":9,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"190","question":"Pick a feeling you’ve experienced before for which there isn’t currently a word in English. Describe the feeling and make up a word for it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":21,"rt":9626,"timeElapsed":107077},{"subjectID":"5af5ss5dne","prolificID":"6683e9097336723a1012955c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2225d628c0b7a282de5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980259098,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":10,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"190","question":"Pick a feeling you’ve experienced before for which there isn’t currently a word in English. Describe the feeling and make up a word for it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":3304,"timeElapsed":110383},{"subjectID":"5af5ss5dne","prolificID":"6683e9097336723a1012955c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2225d628c0b7a282de5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980262068,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":11,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"190","question":"Pick a feeling you’ve experienced before for which there isn’t currently a word in English. Describe the feeling and make up a word for it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":14,"rt":2967,"timeElapsed":113353},{"subjectID":"5af5ss5dne","prolificID":"6683e9097336723a1012955c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2225d628c0b7a282de5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980264175,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":12,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"190","question":"Pick a feeling you’ve experienced before for which there isn’t currently a word in English. Describe the feeling and make up a word for it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":22,"rt":2105,"timeElapsed":115460},{"subjectID":"5af5ss5dne","prolificID":"6683e9097336723a1012955c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2225d628c0b7a282de5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980266028,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":13,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"190","question":"Pick a feeling you’ve experienced before for which there isn’t currently a word in English. Describe the feeling and make up a word for it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":11,"rt":1851,"timeElapsed":117313},{"subjectID":"5af5ss5dne","prolificID":"6683e9097336723a1012955c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2225d628c0b7a282de5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980268286,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":14,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"190","question":"Pick a feeling you’ve experienced before for which there isn’t currently a word in English. Describe the feeling and make up a word for it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":24,"rt":2256,"timeElapsed":119571},{"subjectID":"5af5ss5dne","prolificID":"6683e9097336723a1012955c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2225d628c0b7a282de5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980270711,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":15,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"190","question":"Pick a feeling you’ve experienced before for which there isn’t currently a word in English. Describe the feeling and make up a word for it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":5,"rt":2424,"timeElapsed":121996},{"subjectID":"5af5ss5dne","prolificID":"6683e9097336723a1012955c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2225d628c0b7a282de5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980272502,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":16,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"190","question":"Pick a feeling you’ve experienced before for which there isn’t currently a word in English. Describe the feeling and make up a word for it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":7,"rt":1789,"timeElapsed":123787},{"subjectID":"5af5ss5dne","prolificID":"6683e9097336723a1012955c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2225d628c0b7a282de5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980274307,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":17,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"190","question":"Pick a feeling you’ve experienced before for which there isn’t currently a word in English. Describe the feeling and make up a word for it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":11,"rt":1803,"timeElapsed":125591},{"subjectID":"5af5ss5dne","prolificID":"6683e9097336723a1012955c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2225d628c0b7a282de5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980280933,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":18,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"187","question":"Do you drink caffeine during the day? What kind of caffeine do you drink? How many times a day do you have it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":5793,"timeElapsed":132218},{"subjectID":"5af5ss5dne","prolificID":"6683e9097336723a1012955c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2225d628c0b7a282de5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980285161,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":19,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"187","question":"Do you drink caffeine during the day? What kind of caffeine do you drink? How many times a day do you have it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":36,"rt":4227,"timeElapsed":136446},{"subjectID":"5af5ss5dne","prolificID":"6683e9097336723a1012955c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2225d628c0b7a282de5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980288116,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":20,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"187","question":"Do you drink caffeine during the day? What kind of caffeine do you drink? How many times a day do you have it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":23,"rt":2954,"timeElapsed":139401},{"subjectID":"5af5ss5dne","prolificID":"6683e9097336723a1012955c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2225d628c0b7a282de5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980290052,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":21,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"187","question":"Do you drink caffeine during the day? What kind of caffeine do you drink? How many times a day do you have it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":30,"rt":1933,"timeElapsed":141336},{"subjectID":"5af5ss5dne","prolificID":"6683e9097336723a1012955c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2225d628c0b7a282de5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980292570,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":22,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"187","question":"Do you drink caffeine during the day? What kind of caffeine do you drink? How many times a day do you have it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":71,"rt":2517,"timeElapsed":143855},{"subjectID":"5af5ss5dne","prolificID":"6683e9097336723a1012955c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2225d628c0b7a282de5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980294604,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":23,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"187","question":"Do you drink caffeine during the day? What kind of caffeine do you drink? How many times a day do you have it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":2032,"timeElapsed":145888},{"subjectID":"5af5ss5dne","prolificID":"6683e9097336723a1012955c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2225d628c0b7a282de5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980298728,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":24,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"187","question":"Do you drink caffeine during the day? What kind of caffeine do you drink? How many times a day do you have it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":71,"rt":4123,"timeElapsed":150013},{"subjectID":"5af5ss5dne","prolificID":"6683e9097336723a1012955c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2225d628c0b7a282de5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980301803,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":25,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"187","question":"Do you drink caffeine during the day? What kind of caffeine do you drink? How many times a day do you have it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":33,"rt":3073,"timeElapsed":153088},{"subjectID":"5af5ss5dne","prolificID":"6683e9097336723a1012955c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2225d628c0b7a282de5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980304932,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":26,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"187","question":"Do you drink caffeine during the day? What kind of caffeine do you drink? How many times a day do you have it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":20,"rt":3127,"timeElapsed":156217},{"subjectID":"5af5ss5dne","prolificID":"6683e9097336723a1012955c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2225d628c0b7a282de5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980312447,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":27,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"232","question":"Are there any vegetables you don’t eat? When was the last time you ate one of those things?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":6592,"timeElapsed":163732},{"subjectID":"5af5ss5dne","prolificID":"6683e9097336723a1012955c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2225d628c0b7a282de5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980315236,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":28,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"232","question":"Are there any vegetables you don’t eat? When was the last time you ate one of those things?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":2787,"timeElapsed":166521},{"subjectID":"5af5ss5dne","prolificID":"6683e9097336723a1012955c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2225d628c0b7a282de5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980317988,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":29,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"232","question":"Are there any vegetables you don’t eat? When was the last time you ate one of those things?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":25,"rt":2751,"timeElapsed":169273},{"subjectID":"5af5ss5dne","prolificID":"6683e9097336723a1012955c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2225d628c0b7a282de5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980319871,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":30,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"232","question":"Are there any vegetables you don’t eat? When was the last time you ate one of those things?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":30,"rt":1881,"timeElapsed":171155},{"subjectID":"5af5ss5dne","prolificID":"6683e9097336723a1012955c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2225d628c0b7a282de5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980321692,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":31,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"232","question":"Are there any vegetables you don’t eat? When was the last time you ate one of those things?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":35,"rt":1820,"timeElapsed":172977},{"subjectID":"5af5ss5dne","prolificID":"6683e9097336723a1012955c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2225d628c0b7a282de5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980323027,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":32,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"232","question":"Are there any vegetables you don’t eat? When was the last time you ate one of those things?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":25,"rt":1334,"timeElapsed":174312},{"subjectID":"5af5ss5dne","prolificID":"6683e9097336723a1012955c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2225d628c0b7a282de5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980324686,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":33,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"232","question":"Are there any vegetables you don’t eat? When was the last time you ate one of those things?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":70,"rt":1657,"timeElapsed":175971},{"subjectID":"5af5ss5dne","prolificID":"6683e9097336723a1012955c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2225d628c0b7a282de5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980326516,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":34,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"232","question":"Are there any vegetables you don’t eat? When was the last time you ate one of those things?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":16,"rt":1828,"timeElapsed":177801},{"subjectID":"5af5ss5dne","prolificID":"6683e9097336723a1012955c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2225d628c0b7a282de5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980330048,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":35,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"232","question":"Are there any vegetables you don’t eat? When was the last time you ate one of those things?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":5,"rt":3530,"timeElapsed":181333},{"subjectID":"5af5ss5dne","prolificID":"6683e9097336723a1012955c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2225d628c0b7a282de5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980337046,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":36,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"86","question":"Who do you think is the most underrated artist, performer, or athlete?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":73,"rt":6177,"timeElapsed":188331},{"subjectID":"5af5ss5dne","prolificID":"6683e9097336723a1012955c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2225d628c0b7a282de5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980343378,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":37,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"86","question":"Who do you think is the most underrated artist, performer, or athlete?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":38,"rt":6331,"timeElapsed":194663},{"subjectID":"5af5ss5dne","prolificID":"6683e9097336723a1012955c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2225d628c0b7a282de5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980344803,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":38,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"86","question":"Who do you think is the most underrated artist, performer, or athlete?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":78,"rt":1423,"timeElapsed":196088},{"subjectID":"5af5ss5dne","prolificID":"6683e9097336723a1012955c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2225d628c0b7a282de5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980346236,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":39,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"86","question":"Who do you think is the most underrated artist, performer, or athlete?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":43,"rt":1431,"timeElapsed":197521},{"subjectID":"5af5ss5dne","prolificID":"6683e9097336723a1012955c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2225d628c0b7a282de5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980349730,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":40,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"86","question":"Who do you think is the most underrated artist, performer, or athlete?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":3492,"timeElapsed":201015},{"subjectID":"5af5ss5dne","prolificID":"6683e9097336723a1012955c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2225d628c0b7a282de5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980351569,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":41,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"86","question":"Who do you think is the most underrated artist, performer, or athlete?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":28,"rt":1838,"timeElapsed":202854},{"subjectID":"5af5ss5dne","prolificID":"6683e9097336723a1012955c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2225d628c0b7a282de5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980355640,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":42,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"86","question":"Who do you think is the most underrated artist, performer, or athlete?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":25,"rt":4070,"timeElapsed":206925},{"subjectID":"5af5ss5dne","prolificID":"6683e9097336723a1012955c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2225d628c0b7a282de5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980360442,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":43,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"86","question":"Who do you think is the most underrated artist, performer, or athlete?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":23,"rt":4800,"timeElapsed":211727},{"subjectID":"5af5ss5dne","prolificID":"6683e9097336723a1012955c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2225d628c0b7a282de5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980364257,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":44,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"86","question":"Who do you think is the most underrated artist, performer, or athlete?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":3814,"timeElapsed":215542},{"subjectID":"5af5ss5dne","prolificID":"6683e9097336723a1012955c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2225d628c0b7a282de5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980369972,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":45,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"214","question":"Is there a sound that really bothers you? If so, what is it? If not, has someone ever asked you to stop making a sound because it bothered them?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":5008,"timeElapsed":221257},{"subjectID":"5af5ss5dne","prolificID":"6683e9097336723a1012955c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2225d628c0b7a282de5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980371831,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":46,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"214","question":"Is there a sound that really bothers you? If so, what is it? If not, has someone ever asked you to stop making a sound because it bothered them?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":37,"rt":1857,"timeElapsed":223116},{"subjectID":"5af5ss5dne","prolificID":"6683e9097336723a1012955c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2225d628c0b7a282de5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980373345,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":47,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"214","question":"Is there a sound that really bothers you? If so, what is it? If not, has someone ever asked you to stop making a sound because it bothered them?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":31,"rt":1512,"timeElapsed":224630},{"subjectID":"5af5ss5dne","prolificID":"6683e9097336723a1012955c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2225d628c0b7a282de5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980374535,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":48,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"214","question":"Is there a sound that really bothers you? If so, what is it? If not, has someone ever asked you to stop making a sound because it bothered them?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":24,"rt":1188,"timeElapsed":225820},{"subjectID":"5af5ss5dne","prolificID":"6683e9097336723a1012955c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2225d628c0b7a282de5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980375812,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":49,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"214","question":"Is there a sound that really bothers you? If so, what is it? If not, has someone ever asked you to stop making a sound because it bothered them?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":22,"rt":1276,"timeElapsed":227097},{"subjectID":"5af5ss5dne","prolificID":"6683e9097336723a1012955c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2225d628c0b7a282de5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980380526,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":0,"trialIdx":49,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"Is there a sound that really bothers you? If so, what is it? If not, has someone ever asked you to stop making a sound because it bothered them?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMin":"STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMax":"PINEAPPLE","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":4712,"timeElapsed":231811},{"subjectID":"5af5ss5dne","prolificID":"6683e9097336723a1012955c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2225d628c0b7a282de5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980382583,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":50,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"214","question":"Is there a sound that really bothers you? If so, what is it? If not, has someone ever asked you to stop making a sound because it bothered them?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":27,"rt":2056,"timeElapsed":233868},{"subjectID":"5af5ss5dne","prolificID":"6683e9097336723a1012955c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2225d628c0b7a282de5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980386442,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":51,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"214","question":"Is there a sound that really bothers you? If so, what is it? If not, has someone ever asked you to stop making a sound because it bothered them?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":69,"rt":3858,"timeElapsed":237727},{"subjectID":"5af5ss5dne","prolificID":"6683e9097336723a1012955c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2225d628c0b7a282de5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980389291,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":52,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"214","question":"Is there a sound that really bothers you? If so, what is it? If not, has someone ever asked you to stop making a sound because it bothered them?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":3,"rt":2848,"timeElapsed":240576},{"subjectID":"5af5ss5dne","prolificID":"6683e9097336723a1012955c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2225d628c0b7a282de5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980392562,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":53,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"214","question":"Is there a sound that really bothers you? If so, what is it? If not, has someone ever asked you to stop making a sound because it bothered them?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":12,"rt":3269,"timeElapsed":243847},{"subjectID":"5af5ss5dne","prolificID":"6683e9097336723a1012955c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2225d628c0b7a282de5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980397534,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":54,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"55","question":"What do you think is the purpose of education?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":79,"rt":3665,"timeElapsed":248819},{"subjectID":"5af5ss5dne","prolificID":"6683e9097336723a1012955c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2225d628c0b7a282de5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980399372,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":55,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"55","question":"What do you think is the purpose of education?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":83,"rt":1836,"timeElapsed":250657},{"subjectID":"5af5ss5dne","prolificID":"6683e9097336723a1012955c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2225d628c0b7a282de5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980401436,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":56,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"55","question":"What do you think is the purpose of education?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":2063,"timeElapsed":252720},{"subjectID":"5af5ss5dne","prolificID":"6683e9097336723a1012955c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2225d628c0b7a282de5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980406137,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":57,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"55","question":"What do you think is the purpose of education?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":18,"rt":4700,"timeElapsed":257422},{"subjectID":"5af5ss5dne","prolificID":"6683e9097336723a1012955c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2225d628c0b7a282de5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980408019,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":58,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"55","question":"What do you think is the purpose of education?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":1879,"timeElapsed":259304},{"subjectID":"5af5ss5dne","prolificID":"6683e9097336723a1012955c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2225d628c0b7a282de5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980409738,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":59,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"55","question":"What do you think is the purpose of education?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":28,"rt":1717,"timeElapsed":261023},{"subjectID":"5af5ss5dne","prolificID":"6683e9097336723a1012955c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2225d628c0b7a282de5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980412567,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":60,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"55","question":"What do you think is the purpose of education?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":72,"rt":2827,"timeElapsed":263852},{"subjectID":"5af5ss5dne","prolificID":"6683e9097336723a1012955c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2225d628c0b7a282de5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980415294,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":61,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"55","question":"What do you think is the purpose of education?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":2725,"timeElapsed":266579},{"subjectID":"5af5ss5dne","prolificID":"6683e9097336723a1012955c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2225d628c0b7a282de5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980417672,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":62,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"55","question":"What do you think is the purpose of education?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":2376,"timeElapsed":268956},{"subjectID":"5af5ss5dne","prolificID":"6683e9097336723a1012955c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2225d628c0b7a282de5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980421221,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":100,"trialIdx":62,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"What do you think is the purpose of education?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled HAMBURGER","scaleTextMin":"HOTDOG","scaleTextMax":"HAMBURGER","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":3548,"timeElapsed":272506},{"subjectID":"5af5ss5dne","prolificID":"6683e9097336723a1012955c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2225d628c0b7a282de5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980431712,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":63,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"98","question":"If you had to write your own eulogy to be read at your funeral, what would it say in brief?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":90,"rt":9494,"timeElapsed":282997},{"subjectID":"5af5ss5dne","prolificID":"6683e9097336723a1012955c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2225d628c0b7a282de5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980436527,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":64,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"98","question":"If you had to write your own eulogy to be read at your funeral, what would it say in brief?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":54,"rt":4814,"timeElapsed":287812},{"subjectID":"5af5ss5dne","prolificID":"6683e9097336723a1012955c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2225d628c0b7a282de5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980438296,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":65,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"98","question":"If you had to write your own eulogy to be read at your funeral, what would it say in brief?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":79,"rt":1767,"timeElapsed":289581},{"subjectID":"5af5ss5dne","prolificID":"6683e9097336723a1012955c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2225d628c0b7a282de5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980440061,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":66,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"98","question":"If you had to write your own eulogy to be read at your funeral, what would it say in brief?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":1764,"timeElapsed":291346},{"subjectID":"5af5ss5dne","prolificID":"6683e9097336723a1012955c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2225d628c0b7a282de5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980443166,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":67,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"98","question":"If you had to write your own eulogy to be read at your funeral, what would it say in brief?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":88,"rt":3103,"timeElapsed":294451},{"subjectID":"5af5ss5dne","prolificID":"6683e9097336723a1012955c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2225d628c0b7a282de5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980444842,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":68,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"98","question":"If you had to write your own eulogy to be read at your funeral, what would it say in brief?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":74,"rt":1675,"timeElapsed":296127},{"subjectID":"5af5ss5dne","prolificID":"6683e9097336723a1012955c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2225d628c0b7a282de5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980447148,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":69,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"98","question":"If you had to write your own eulogy to be read at your funeral, what would it say in brief?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":93,"rt":2304,"timeElapsed":298433},{"subjectID":"5af5ss5dne","prolificID":"6683e9097336723a1012955c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2225d628c0b7a282de5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980448686,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":70,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"98","question":"If you had to write your own eulogy to be read at your funeral, what would it say in brief?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":87,"rt":1536,"timeElapsed":299970},{"subjectID":"5af5ss5dne","prolificID":"6683e9097336723a1012955c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2225d628c0b7a282de5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980451931,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":71,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"98","question":"If you had to write your own eulogy to be read at your funeral, what would it say in brief?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":90,"rt":3244,"timeElapsed":303216},{"subjectID":"5af5ss5dne","prolificID":"6683e9097336723a1012955c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2225d628c0b7a282de5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980458787,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":72,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"36","question":"Describe a time you felt most full of joy.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":84,"rt":6050,"timeElapsed":310072},{"subjectID":"5af5ss5dne","prolificID":"6683e9097336723a1012955c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2225d628c0b7a282de5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980460506,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":73,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"36","question":"Describe a time you felt most full of joy.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":86,"rt":1718,"timeElapsed":311791},{"subjectID":"5af5ss5dne","prolificID":"6683e9097336723a1012955c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2225d628c0b7a282de5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980461789,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":74,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"36","question":"Describe a time you felt most full of joy.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":69,"rt":1282,"timeElapsed":313074},{"subjectID":"5af5ss5dne","prolificID":"6683e9097336723a1012955c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2225d628c0b7a282de5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980463257,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":75,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"36","question":"Describe a time you felt most full of joy.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":79,"rt":1465,"timeElapsed":314542},{"subjectID":"5af5ss5dne","prolificID":"6683e9097336723a1012955c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2225d628c0b7a282de5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980465672,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":76,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"36","question":"Describe a time you felt most full of joy.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":93,"rt":2413,"timeElapsed":316957},{"subjectID":"5af5ss5dne","prolificID":"6683e9097336723a1012955c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2225d628c0b7a282de5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980468404,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":77,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"36","question":"Describe a time you felt most full of joy.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":77,"rt":2731,"timeElapsed":319689},{"subjectID":"5af5ss5dne","prolificID":"6683e9097336723a1012955c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2225d628c0b7a282de5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980470720,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":78,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"36","question":"Describe a time you felt most full of joy.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":88,"rt":2314,"timeElapsed":322005},{"subjectID":"5af5ss5dne","prolificID":"6683e9097336723a1012955c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2225d628c0b7a282de5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980473308,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":79,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"36","question":"Describe a time you felt most full of joy.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":96,"rt":2587,"timeElapsed":324593},{"subjectID":"5af5ss5dne","prolificID":"6683e9097336723a1012955c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2225d628c0b7a282de5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980475265,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":80,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"36","question":"Describe a time you felt most full of joy.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":77,"rt":1956,"timeElapsed":326550},{"subjectID":"5af5ss5dne","prolificID":"6683e9097336723a1012955c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2225d628c0b7a282de5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980487017,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":81,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"222","question":"When was the last time you stopped to appreciate nature? Describe where you were and what you were doing.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":10707,"timeElapsed":338302},{"subjectID":"5af5ss5dne","prolificID":"6683e9097336723a1012955c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2225d628c0b7a282de5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980490917,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":82,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"222","question":"When was the last time you stopped to appreciate nature? Describe where you were and what you were doing.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":70,"rt":3898,"timeElapsed":342202},{"subjectID":"5af5ss5dne","prolificID":"6683e9097336723a1012955c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2225d628c0b7a282de5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980492425,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":83,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"222","question":"When was the last time you stopped to appreciate nature? Describe where you were and what you were doing.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":72,"rt":1507,"timeElapsed":343710},{"subjectID":"5af5ss5dne","prolificID":"6683e9097336723a1012955c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2225d628c0b7a282de5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980495741,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":84,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"222","question":"When was the last time you stopped to appreciate nature? Describe where you were and what you were doing.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":28,"rt":3314,"timeElapsed":347026},{"subjectID":"5af5ss5dne","prolificID":"6683e9097336723a1012955c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2225d628c0b7a282de5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980498088,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":85,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"222","question":"When was the last time you stopped to appreciate nature? Describe where you were and what you were doing.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":69,"rt":2345,"timeElapsed":349373},{"subjectID":"5af5ss5dne","prolificID":"6683e9097336723a1012955c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2225d628c0b7a282de5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980500128,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":86,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"222","question":"When was the last time you stopped to appreciate nature? Describe where you were and what you were doing.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":20,"rt":2039,"timeElapsed":351413},{"subjectID":"5af5ss5dne","prolificID":"6683e9097336723a1012955c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2225d628c0b7a282de5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980501636,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":87,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"222","question":"When was the last time you stopped to appreciate nature? Describe where you were and what you were doing.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":81,"rt":1506,"timeElapsed":352920},{"subjectID":"5af5ss5dne","prolificID":"6683e9097336723a1012955c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2225d628c0b7a282de5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980503557,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":88,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"222","question":"When was the last time you stopped to appreciate nature? Describe where you were and what you were doing.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":32,"rt":1920,"timeElapsed":354842},{"subjectID":"5af5ss5dne","prolificID":"6683e9097336723a1012955c","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2225d628c0b7a282de5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980505686,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":89,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"222","question":"When was the last time you stopped to appreciate nature? Describe where you were and what you were doing.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":78,"rt":2127,"timeElapsed":356971}]